Marist Student Government Association Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Marist Student Government Association Collection
1983 - 2016
npkmc-235-041
Marist College Student Government Association (SGA)
28 Boxes 11.5 Linear Feet
This collection showcases the activities of the Student Government Association at Marist College from 1983 to present day. Materials included in this collection encompass documents produced by the SGA for meetings, SGA legislation, clubs, events, allocations to clubs, reports, correspondence, and other related materials.
Marist College Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road Poughkeepsie, NY Poughkeepsie New York 12601 United States
There are no restrictions on this collection.
The Marist Student Government Association began in 1983 with the Galanti Administration. The organization has run uninterrupted since its inception. The SGA works to empower the student body of Marist College and serve as a liaison between the student body and the administration. In doing this, the SGA provides guidance to other student groups, clubs, and organizations. Additionally, the SGA approves charters and funds campus clubs and organizations.
In 1993, the Rhinehart Administration established the constitution of the Marist SGA. The document was passed unanimously by the members of the assembly, and since its adoption, it has been amended 27 times. The document established the role and purpose of the SGA, the assembly, the various different officer positions, and the different branches of the government. The bylaws of the SGA were passed unanimously by the members of the Senate in February 2005. These bylaws have been amended over the years and help provide guidance to the behavior and expectations of the SGA and its members.
As of 2023, the SGA is responsible for the funding, support, and management of over 90 student organizations, including club sports, social and professional Greek life, and a range of other social and academic clubs. The SGA is also responsible for the approval of parking ticket appeals, running of projects to support the Marist campus, and representing and advocating for the students on and off campus. In 2023, the SGA completed a large revision of the constitution and bylaws, which included specifying specific elements of passing legislation, reclassifying the cabinet position from Student Body Historian to Student Body Archivist, and defining and redefining officer positions within the SGA.
Materials in this collection all pertain to the running and functioning of the SGA. Materials include meeting minutes, proposed and approved pieces of legislation for the SGA, documents related to the activities, discipline, and operation of clubs at Marist, event planning documents and fliers, and SGA reports on activities and reports received from other areas of campus. Materials also includes SGA funding allocation information for clubs and SGA correspondence.
Marist College (Poughkeepsie, N.Y.); Student government
This collection is organized into series by calendar year, each series is divided into the subseries: meetings, legislation, clubs, events, allocations, reports, correspondence, and misc.
Materials have been donated to the Marist Archives & Special Collections by various SGA officers during their time in the SGA.
Materials are received on an on-going basis from the SGA. As of February 2023, the SGA Archivist is to deposit materials with the Marist Archives & Special Collections at the end of each semester.
College Archives College Archives Photo Collection
- 1. 1983
  Extent: 1 folder
  - Correspondence, circa 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 2. 1986
  - Correspondence, circa 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 3. 1987
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to clubs, events, and allocations.
  - Subseries 3.1: Clubs
    - Circle K Issue (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3.2: Events
    - Teacher Recognition Award Form, February 14, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3.3: Allocations
    - MCCU Allocation Requests (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 4. 1988
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to events, allocations, and correspondence.
  - Subseries 4.1 Events
    - Commuter Union Halloween Dance, October 28, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 4.2 Allocations
    Extent: 2 folders
    - MCCU Allocations, November 18, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Radio City Music Hall Allocations (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 4.2 Correspondence
    - Correspondence, June 10, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 5. 1989
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, clubs, events, allocations, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 5.1 Meetings
    - Meetings Notebook 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 5.2: Clubs
    - Circle K Issue, April 1, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 5.3: Events
    - MCCU: "Road Trip" Event, October 6, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Christmas Spectacular Event (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 5.4: Allocations
    - Commuter Union Allocations (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 5.5: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 5.6: Misc.
    - MCCU Misc. Flyers/Papers (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 6. 1990
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, clubs, and misc.
  - Subseries 6.1: Meetings
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Charter Review, September 20, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 6.2: Clubs
    - Commuter Union Allocations (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 6.3: Misc.
    - Responsibilities of SA Personnel (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 7. 1991
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, clubs, events, allocations, and correspondence.
  - Subseries 7.1: Meetings
    - Council of Student Leaders Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 7.2: Legislation
    Extent: 4 folders
    - Foxfest '91, July 10, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - ID Bracelet Proposal, July 20, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - CSL Structure Change, July 20, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - CSL Organizational Changes Approval, August 4, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 7.3: Events
    Extent: 5 folders
    - Circle K - Youth Motivator, February 4, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Circle K - Newsletter, February 1, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Circle K - Come Back to the Beach, March 2, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Circle K Issues (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Circle K Misc. Papers (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Subseries 7.4: Allocations
    - Commuter Union Allocations (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Subseries 7.5: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 31)
- 8. 1992
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, clubs, allocations, reports, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 8.1: Meetings
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Council of Student leaders Meetings, Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Student Life Committee Meetings (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 8.2: Legislation
    - Meet Marist Market Proposal, March 1, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - S.E.G.A./C.S.L. Event Proposals, Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Tentative" Schedule, Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Proposal for Article X (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Recycling Policy Proposal (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - SLC Fall '92 Calendar, Fall 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 8.3: Clubs
    - American Chemical Society Constitution and By-laws (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Circle K Issues (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Financial Board Guidelines for Clubs (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Student Life Council By-laws, January 30, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - TKE Incident, October 27, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Women's Lacrosse By-laws (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 8.4: Allocations
    - Student Life Committee Allocations (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 8.5 Reports
    - Housing Population Projection (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Marist College Judicial Board Guidelines (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - The Relationship Between Marist College and Student Clubs/Government, July 15, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Student Academic Council Survey, December 9, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 8.6: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 8.7: Misc.
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 9. 1993
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, clubs, events, allocations, reports, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 9.1: Meetings
    Extent: 9 folders
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Senate Ad-Hoc Committee on Club-caps (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Senate Meetings (Duplicates) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Student Life Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Vision '94 Construction Committee Meeting, April 28, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 9.2: Legislation
    - Proposed Amendment Change for SGA Constitution (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Quiet Hour and Guess Pass Proposal (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Parliamentarian Proposal (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Recycling Policy for Student Handbook (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - SLC Issue Proposal, February 10, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 9.3: Clubs
    Extent: 19 folders
    - Academic Standards for Greek Life (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - American Chemical Society By-laws (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Amnesty International By-laws (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Marist College Band By-laws Draft #3 + Revision, February 18, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - The Club Capping Model, April 26, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Clubs and Organizations List (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Golf Team By-laws, December 8, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - International Italian-American Society By-laws (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma: Zeta Chi Bylaws, 1905-06-15 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Mathematics Club By-laws (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - MCCTA By-laws +Amendment (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Model United Nations By-laws (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Political Science Club By-laws (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - R.A.W. Interactions By-laws (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Resident Student Council Misc. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Student Life Council Events Calendars, 1905-06-15 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - SLC Names+Numbers, 1905-06-15 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - SGA Constitution, March 28, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Women's Lacrosse By-laws (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 9.4: Events
    - Proposal for Escort Extravaganza, December 1, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Event Evaluation Forms (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Final Exams Service Program (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Paint Pellet Wars (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Subseries 9.5: Allocations
    Extent: 13 folders
    - All Sport High School Rental Rates + Requirements, December 19, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Budget Adjustments, November 19, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Class of '95 Budget Allocations, Spring 1993 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Club Allocations (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Fall '93 Allocations, March 22, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Funding Requests (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - RSC Allocations (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Student Life Council Allocations (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - SLC Spring '93 Budget, Spring 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Spring '93 Additional Allocations, Spring 1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Spring '94 Budget Requests, December 9, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Student Life Council Support Basket Program (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - 1993 Allocation Budget, Fall 1993 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Subseries 9.6: Reports
    - Chief Justice's Reports, March 8, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - SGA Club Reviews, August 22-23, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Election Commissioner's Report: Class of '95 Presidential Election Investigation (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Election Commissioner's Report: Student Body Presidential Election Investigation (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Election Procedures and Guidelines (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Guidelines for Class Officers (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Marist College Judicial Board Appeal Guidelines (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Relationship Between Marist College and Student Clubs/Government (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - SGA - Comission on Safety & Security (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Student Life Council Committee Reports (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Student Life Council End of Year Questionnaire (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Security Reports for SLC (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Student Life Council Final Report (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 9.7: Correspondence
    Extent: 3 folders
    - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Dennis Murray: Update on College Activities, September 6, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Memorandun - President Murray (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 9.8: Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - SGA Update Volume 1, Jan/Feb 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 10. 1994
  - Subseries 10.1: Meetings
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - SLC Meetings (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 10.2: Legislation
    - MCCTA Proposal (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 10.3: Clubs
    Extent: 6 folders
    - Alpha Sigma Tau By-laws (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - RSC Constitution (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Resident Student Council Rosters, September 29, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Singers By-laws, February 19, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Student Programming Council By-laws (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Women's Club By-laws (Women's Awareness Club) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 10.4: Events
    - Proposal for Escort Extravaganza, February 23, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Earth Day 1994, April 30, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Spring 1994 Elections, February, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Subseries 10.5: Allocations
    - Additional Allocations '94 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Campus Fund Raiser Info (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - College Bank '94 Allocations (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Spring '95 Financial Requests, December 2, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Student Life Council Allocations (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Support Baskets '94 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Subseries 10.6: Reports
    - Club Committee Report for March 7 Senate Meeting, March 7, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Investigation of Greek Cap (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Subseries 10.7: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Subseries 10.8: Misc.
    - Impeachment of Daryl Ledyard (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Robin Ward: SLC Application for Officer's Position (Box 4, Folder 39)
- 11. 1995
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, clubs, allocations, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 11.1: Meetings
    - Senate Meetings [1 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Senate Meetings [2 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Summer Session Schedule (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 11.2: Legislation
    - Proposed Amendment to the Disciplinary Matrix, November 14, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 12:30 Visitation Policy Proposals (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 11.3: Clubs
    - Alpha Phi Delta Community Service List (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Financial Board Guidelines (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Greek Advisory Council Guidelines, November 25, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Greek Council Operations + Procedures, February 13, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Poughkeepsie Institute (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow By-laws (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Women's Awareness Club By-laws (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 11.4: Allocations
    - Allocations List (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Club Allocations for 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Spring '95 Additional Allocations, February 16, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Support Baskets '95 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 11.5: Reports
    - Re-investigation of the Greek Cap, February 3, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Club Review, October 9, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Student Academic Council: Library Survey (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 11.6: Correspondence
    - Memoranda/Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 20)
- 12. 1996
  - Subseries 12.1: Meetings
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 12.2: Legislation
    - World Wide Web Committee Proposal, February 7, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - SGA Coat of Arms Proposal, March 18, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Faculty/Student Affairs Committee Proposal, April 10, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Research and Oversight Committee Proposal, April 17, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Safety and Security Committee Proposal, April 25, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - New Student Life Committee Proposal (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Subseries 12.3: Clubs
    Extent: 7 folders
    - Club Affairs Council By-laws, February 16, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - P.E.O.P.L.E. By-laws, February 14, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon By-laws (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Public Relations Committee By-laws (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Society of Professional Journalists By-laws, October 7, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Student Academic Council By-laws (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Student Programming Council By-laws, February, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Subseries 12.4: Allocations
    - Financial Board Allocations (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Spring '96 Additional Allocations, February 12, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Subseries 12.5: Correspondence
    - Memoranda/Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Spring Elections Results, February 23, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Subseries 12.6: Misc.
    - Listing of Club Codes, October 22, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Off-Campus Properties (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - SGA Extensions (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 13. 1997
  - Subseries 13.1: Meetings
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates - Hand-written] (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board Minutes (Floppy Disk) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Joint Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Parliamentary Procedure Workshop (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - RSC/CSC Leadership Conference (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates-Handwritten] (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - SGA Leadership Conference, September 12, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Student Life Council Meetings (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 13.2: Legislation
    Extent: 20 folders
    - Priority Points for Employment, April 2, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Proposed SGA Constitutional Amendments, July 5, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Legislation, August 2, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Mission Statement for Battle of the Bands, August 11, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Student Core/Liberal Arts Committee, August 27, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Legislation, August 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Mission Statement for Class of 1999, September 3, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Legislation, September 4, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Lundy Bill for Amending S00010, September 9, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Legislation, September 10, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Legislation, September 15, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Legislation, September 17, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Legislation, September 23, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - The Year of Action Bill, September 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Legislation, October 1, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Legislation, October 21, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Legislation, October 28, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Legislation, November 4, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, November 19, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Legislation, November 24, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 13.3: Clubs
    - Computer Society By-laws (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - How to Create Your Club's By-laws (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Official WMCR "Big Plan" (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Poughkeepsie Institute (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - SGA Constitution (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Sigma Iota Alpha By-laws (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 13.4: Events
    - Election Results Fall 1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 13.5: Allocations
    - Fall '97 Additional Allocations, September 26, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Spring '97 Allocations, November 19, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Spring '98 Allocations, December 1, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 13.6: Reports
    - Middle States Periodic Review Report (First Draft), May 1, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Goals and Objectives, June 27, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cafeteria Survey Report 3 Copies, Summer 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Suggestions for West Cedar, October 31, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Executive Plan of Action Agreement (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Student Government Poll (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 13.7: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 13.8: Misc.
    - North End Burglary Warning Flyers, November 17, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Misc. (Box 7, Folder 24)
- 14. 1998
  - Subseries 14.1: Meetings
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - General Meetings (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Joint Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Leadership Conference - Summer Session, July 18, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Institute Working Group (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates - Hand-written] (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - SLC Meetings (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - SGA Informal Meeting, January 23, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 14.2: Legislation
    Extent: 27 folders
    - Legislation, February 24, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Constitutional Change - Quorum, February 25, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Svare, Hogan Bill for Bookstore Discounts, March 3, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, March 5, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Maduri Bill for Giving Tree Organization, March 25, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Priority Point Distribution Committee, April 6, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Fall Elections Calendar, April 27, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Legislation, April 28, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Legislation, July 15, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Legislation, July 18, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Legislation, July 19, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Improving Campus Communications, August 27, December 4, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Commuter Activities Commission Mission Statement, August 28, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Legislation, September 7, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Mission Statement for the Student Core/Liberal Arts Committee, September 8, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Joint Resolution in Support of a Crosswalk, September 9, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Referendum Question for the Fall 1998 Election Ballot, September 15, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Amendment to the Fall 1998 Referendum Question, September 21, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - 1998-1999 Diversity Day Organizational Committee Mission Statement, October 7, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Legislation, November 2, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Spring 1999 Elections Calendar, November 9, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Spring 2000 Budget Bill, November 11, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 1999 Spring Budget Bill, November 12, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Commuter Lounge Relocation Committee, November 23, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - The Svare/Tyminski Bill for Election Results Clarification, November 29, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 29)